This is the target I must execute:
The otherworlder, Akari Tokitou.
Even if she is killed,
she possesses the Pure Concept of Time
that lets her rewind time to before her death.
Invoke [Regression]
According to Archbishop Orwell,
there's a ceremonial hall that can eliminate even
an anomaly like Akari in the ancient capital of Garm.
Thus, I lied to Akari so that we
could set off together for Garm.
Go ahead and enjoy the trip, Akari.
Because when this journey ends, the thing that awaits...
...is the end of your life.
Carriage 4
Episode 3: Taboo in [Red]
Carriage 1
VIP Carriage
What a foolish thing my father has done.
To think he summoned otherworlders in thirst for power...
You're Princess Ashuna?
Indeed.
I am the youngest daughter of King Grisarika,
Ashuna Grisarika.
And...
Who might you lot be?
Carriage 5
Listen up!
You'd better stay quiet!
You'll get what's coming to you if you resist!
Menou, what's the deal with those people?
Some typical dissatisfied members of society.
I guess you could call them terrorists.
Does this kind of thing happen a lot?
Of course not.
Honestly, talk about bad luck.
Don't you move!
They have guns in this world, too?
Those are etheric guns.
Though they're actually illegal.
Hey!
What are you two blabbering on about-
Crap, a priestess.
Good day, Mr. Terrorist.
I'm simply a clergywoman who serves the helpless.
Is there a problem?
Get up.
You priestesses can be dangerous.
You can start by putting your scripture on the floor.
And after that...
Take all your clothes off.
Who knows what weapons you might be hiding?
Well, I am hiding a dagger,
so it's not totally unreasonable, but...
Get on with it!
Pipe down, will you? I heard you just fine.
I'll pretend to undress to get his guard down, and then...
W-wait just a second!
Don't do anything awful to Menou!
I'll undress in her place, okay?!
D-don't worry. I won't let him abuse you, Menou!
I'm sorry, Akari.
You're not making any sense.
Could you not talk for a moment?
Nah, I don't really mind whichever.
Lay off. She's just an ordinary girl.
What you want is to disarm me, isn't it?
For starters, here's my scripture.
There, here you GO!
W-why you...!
Menou, you're amaz-
Shh!
Please keep quiet, everyone.
There might be more of them in the other carriages.
That should do it.
Listen Akari...
You're a fool if you think you could protect me.
Don't do anything dangerous, all right?
S-sure...
I'm sorry.
But...
Thanks anyway.
It made me happy that you were so brave, Akari.
Well then, I'm going to go take out the others,
so be a good girl and wait here.
Menou!
Please be careful.
I don't want to be left behind anymore!
I'll be fine. See you soon.
"Anymore"?
Carriage 2
What an unlucky gang of idiots.
You just had to choose this train to attack.
Now, tell me what you want
and how many of you there are.
No way...
Not to a little brat like you...
Oh, I see how it is. If you're not going to talk...
I'm going to start sawing at your throat with this.
Let's see if you start talking,
or if I'll saw off that head of yours first.
Which will it be, I wonder?
Carriage 4
I see...
So they're after the Princess Ashuna Grisarika.
Yes...
They intended to take her hostage and demand
the release of their captured terrorist leader.
How idiotic.
How many of them are there?
Thirteen in all.
Five went to the first class carriage where the princess is,
and two went to the engine room.
For starters, I'll go secure the engine room.
VIP Carriage
Carriage 1
Yes, please do that.
Miss!
Thank you for getting rid of the bad guys!
You're very welcome.
Oh?
What an adorable but unexpected guest.
Good day to you.
I'm a princess of the kingdom
and a knight in my own right-
Your Highness, the Princess Knight Ashuna Grisarika.
Your fame precedes you.
Oh?
And who might you be?
A priestess by the name of Momo.
I'm a white robe, as you can see.
An inexperienced novice.
I like the alterations you've done to your priestess robe.
The human body is beautiful as it is.
Clothing is meant to show off the beauty
of the bodyline instead of concealing it.
That's very kind of you.
But how fortuitous that you came at this moment.
There's something I wish to ask you.
What is it you want?
Oh, not much.
It's just that my father is on trial for heresy at the moment.
I have something of a bone to pick with the Faust.
Is that Momo... and Princess Ashuna?
I have heard that is the case.
But we have yet to know whether
your father actually committed heresy-
Oh? This is a surprise.
What's... this...?
You intend to cut a priestess down just
because you have beef with the Faust?
I intended to stop short, of course.
If I had swung this royal crested sword with full force,
you know a mere fret saw blade
would never have stopped it.
You're awfully self-confident.
Then what's the big idea?
Are they arguing?
Well, I suppose Momo will be fine on her own.
I guess I'll have to go to the engine room instead.
The otherworlders who my father supposedly
summoned are nowhere to be seen.
Perhaps they have been eliminated already...
...at the hands of those infamous
Executioners of the Faust.
"Executioners"? We have nothing of the sort.
Seeing you has made me wonder...
If the executioner finished her job
and left the royal capital,
perhaps she would be riding this very train.
I daresay your imagination has gotten the better of you.
Has it?
I have never once doubted the intuition
that the heavens bestow upon me.
Invoke
Flameburst
Barrier
The Faust truly are skilled.
Your quick decision to protect your head was brilliant.
What do you mean?
I can't have you searing my ribbons now, can I?
A girl's sense of style is all-important, you know.
You think so, too? I enjoy dressing lavishly myself.
I don't want some rich girl likening her causal
indulgence for finery with my sense of fashion.
I like all things strong and beautiful.
Obviously, your strength is worthy
of my attention too, Momo.
Ugh, no thanks.
Double Invoke
Anchor, Oscillation
You've decided to indulge me, after all?
Would you like to see how long that arcane
royal trinket of yours can manage against this?!
It's good to see you're both all right.
Sorry we had you concerned, Priestess!
As you can see we're all fine here,
including the etheric engine.
Our Princess Knight knocked 'em out in one blow!
You know her?
Princess Ashuna,
famous for going 'round righting wrongs!
Why yes, I know of her. It's unfortunate I just missed-
You there, you're only pretending you're knocked out.
What do you have implanted in your bodies?
Busted, eh?
But you're too late.
If we don't make it to Garm we're
gonna be hanged, anyway!
Everyone on this train is going down with us!
It can't be...
Is that a primary red gem?
We were told to swallow them, just in case!
Get out of here before you get sucked in!
B-but if we leave our stations...
I'll figure it out! Hurry!
We'll leave it to you, Priestess!
Ether:
Merge Materials
Activate
[Primary Red,
Armored Knight]
It may not have technique but it's got brute force.
At least it didn't manifest as an angel or a dragon,
I suppose.
If I can just buy some time to wear it down...!
Jeez, is Momo still fighting?
What's wrong, Momo?
You've done nothing but evade so far.
Could you please stop calling me by my name?
Okay, widdle princess?
Now that was interesting!
I don't want to hear it!
Seemingly haphazard but actually
thoroughly calculated...
You used magecraft to make it
come flying back, didn't you?
But before it does...!
Anchor, Oscillation
Are you sure about this, Momo?
I'll force this blade right through.
I'd like to see you try.
Did her saw blade do this?!
Serves you rig-
You crappy little princess!
Momo...?
Ooh, ouch...
Even with etheric enhancement, that was pretty rough...
If only you had died.
With all my training,
a trifle like this isn't enough to do me in.
Same goes for you, doesn't it?
The control valve!
You stupid doll!
It's out of control. That's not good.
At this rate...
This train will run off the rails,
or crash into another train at a station...!
I don't have the time to be dealing with this thing!
What on earth?
What was that?
That was... disturbing.
Just now, something bizarre just happened.
That's all I can tell.
But this... feels familiar somehow...
Menou!
Akari!
Invoke
Gale
T-thanks. You're so strong, Menou!
But what's the deal with that red person?!
More importantly...
Why did you come? Answer me!
W-well, because the men tied
up suddenly got all mangled
and the red lights went
towards the front of the train...
So why would you go after them?!
I told you to be a good girl and stay where you were,
remember?!
I was a good girl just worried about you, Menou!
You should be proud of me!
Why would I be proud?!
If Akari were to get taken in by that thing,
I'll have worse to worry about than
the train not being able to stop!
This is such a hassle!
I didn't really want to do this...
Double Invoke
Thread, Gale
I'm going to channel my ether into it!
Command
Self Destruct
Of course. It won't let me in that easily.
But...!
Etheric Connect-Scripture,
10:9-Invoke
[For so long as thou seekest bliss,
there will be one to bear thy calamity.]
Self Destruct
There! Now perish!
Wow! Amazing, Menou!
If you hadn't come,
I could have taken it down
without using this much ether...
Could it be I was in the way or somethi-?
Totally in the way!
S-sowwy!
It's still out of control...
I have to do something.
I could use magecraft to stop the train,
but I've used too much ether.
I just don't have enough energy left
to conjure on a scale that big...
Akari...
Hmm? What's up?
M-Menou, don't stare at me so
intently or you'll make me blush!
I know this shouldn't really be allowed...
Akari, will you trust me?
Of course!
I always trust you, Menou!
Then listen to what I'm about to say.
M-M-M-M-Menou?!
Why are we here?! It's freaking me out!
Calm down, Akari.
I can't! It doesn't help that you're looking all stern!
Is this better?
You definitely look cuter when you smile, Menou.
Your smile's so dippy, it's as if nothing bad's happening.
You mean that as a compliment, right?
Of course.
Akari, I don't have nearly enough ether to
cast the magecraft needed to stop this train.
So I want to borrow some of yours.
O-okay...
This will hurt a lot.
A person's body always reacts violently when
connecting one's ether to someone else's.
I'm sorry.
Well, I don't like pain... but will you be okay, Menou?
I'll be fine.
You see, I lost most of who I was a long time ago.
That's why I can connect my ether
to others without any pain.
Got it.
Then I'll be okay, too.
I'm fine leaving everything up to you, Menou.
Thanks!
Let's do this.
Okay.
Etheric Connect-Scripture,
8:12-Remote Invoke
[Kneel before the front gate,
for its path leads to the Lord.]
First, I'm going to embed my magecraft
into the earthen vein.
Then, I conjure a gate to draw the train to it,
and add more power!
Here we go, Akari!
Etheric Connect-Scripture,
8:12-Remote Invoke
[Kneel before the front gate,
for its path leads to the Lord.]
Etheric Connect
-Akari Tokitou-
Extract
[Force]
Incredible...
So this is the sheer amount of
ether otherworlders have.
This tickles...
And her body's isn't reacting that violently at all.
But there's no time to be surprised. Not right now!
Medium, Menou
-Etheric Boost-
Maintain Invoke
[Kneel before the front gate,
for its path leads to the Lord.]
Menou...
Please!
Menou!
You did it. Wow, Menou. You're amazing!
Of course.
Because priestesses are supposed
to be pure, just, and strong!
The heavens must truly smile down upon me,
to have allowed this encounter with you!
Now, what will your next move be?!
I've gotten involved with such a nuisance...
We're currently preparing a substitute train.
Please hold on for just a while longer!
Miss!
Millie! It's so great that you're safe!
Yeah! You too!
What if I had failed to stop the train?
Maybe that actually happened once.
Maybe I died, along with all the other passengers...
And then maybe Akari...
Turned back time?
Akari.
Just what kind of power does your
Pure Concept have concealed within?
Next Episode
The Ancient Capital Garm
Next Episode: The Ancient Capital Garm.